

Svetlana Kozlova

FRONT-FND DFVFI OPFR





CONTACT



+375 33 649 59 47



atevs7@inbox.ru



Minsk, Belarus



<u>Telegram</u>

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming. I have experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript. Now I am improving my skills in this direction. I also studying React Native, because I am interesting in mobile development.

SKILLS

- React/Redux/Redux Toolkit
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML&CSS/SCSS
- Axios/Rest API
- Unit tests/StoryBook
- Material UI
- Postman
- Formik
- Git/GitHub

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate (in progress) Russian - Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

Part-time iob Dec 2022-Present

- React development using Redux, React-redux, Redux-thunk, Redux Toolkit, React Router Dom, Axios, Formik, Material UI.
- Checking the correctness of the code with Unit Tests, practice TDD.
- Applying Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application.
- Using TypeScript for the best code control during development.
- Using memo, useMemo, useCallback for reducing re-renders.
- · Design of elements corresponding to the layout of figma, adaptive site layout.

Engineer

Febr 2017- Febr 2023

- Development of the scheme and plan of electrical substations.
- Calculation and installation of high-voltage equipment
- Communication with customers, contractors and experts.

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer 2022

BNTU

Eelectrical systems, engineer 2012-2017